<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:31:24 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7 Day 1000 Word Challenge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/7-day-1000-word-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:31:24 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/7-day-1000-word-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have decided with (semi-purposefully) little forethought and ample reckless&#xA;abandon, that I am going to write 1,000 words everyday for the next week. And I&#xA;am going to publish said 1,000 words each day on this here Substack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will allow myself to not write 1,000 words each day if not able to (like if I&#xA;go on a climbing trip or such), but theoretically I can type at about 80 words&#xA;per minute, which if you do the math (I can&amp;rsquo;t do now because I need to type or&#xA;everything will explode) should mean that I can at least physically type out&#xA;all the words in 15 minutes 12.5 minutes. I will of course have to try and&#xA;think about something that might be half interesting to say at any given point&#xA;[tk. I can tell that I have lost the plot with this sentence/paragraph I was&#xA;supposed to be talking about how I could skip a day, anyway!] but I&amp;rsquo;ll cross&#xA;bridge. How fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:24:55 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 class=&#34;heading&#34; id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Hello world!&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#hello-world&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This simply a dummy post that will allow me to tell if the page will render&#xA;correctly and then I can get to setting up the GitHub page to host this!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Will this work in real time? &lt;strong&gt;Yes sir it will!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Okay now I will try and post the substack article that I wrote a bit ago.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
